



Full-Stack developer specializing in javascript and experienced in graphic design.

I have communication, organizational, and teamwork skills acquired through my education and work experience.

These skills have allowed me to complete a coding bootcamp with +800 hours of intensive training in agile methodologies, pair programming, app development, data structure and algorithms.

Education

Plataforma 5 Coding Bootcamp

Full Stack Developer | 09/2021 - 12/2021

Universidad Nacional de Córdoba (UNC)

Film & TV | Audiovisual Production | 2016 - 2018

Instituto Dr. Facundo de Zuviría

Bachelor in Informatics | MS Office | 2010 - 2014

Skills

Front End

- React
- Redux
- Express
- Material UI
- Bootstrap
- CSS

Design

- Photoshop
- Ilustrator
- Premiere
- Lightroom

Back End

- Mongoose
- PostgreSQL
- Node.js
- Sequelize
- Mongo Atlas
- Postman

Languages

- Advanced English
- Native Spanish

Projects



Adpop | Trading App

• Developed by 2 programmers, a graphic designer and an economist. An app that provides free information about money management, cryptocurrencies, investment opportunities and fraud prevention.

React | Sass | Spreadsheet | React Fade



STORY I E-Commerce

• I created a website to sell my photos as prints in different formats and sizes.

React | Redux | MongoDB | CSS | JWT



KOFE I E-Commerce

• Commercialization for the consumption and processing of coffee, created by a team of 4 web developers.

React | Redux | PostgresSQL | Sequelize | Express.js | Tailwind

Work Experience

Coderhouse

Tutor Diseño Gráfico | 2022 - Actualidad

 Tutor de Diseño Gráfico, asistiendo al profesor durante el dictado de clases y corrigiendo trabajos.

Freelance

Graphic Design & Photography | 2017 - Present

• Freelance photographer and graphic designer with regular clients due to punctual and high quality work.

Santander Bank

Debt collection and credits | 2019-2021

• Customer service, consolidation of payments and credit management.





